she's sharp she's fearless i don't know what they told you but if they told you that cut me off is
how i'm gonna get clicks stop it now she's that girl and she's bringing all of that to your radio
this summer amanda seals is here i am amanda seals comedian artist actress activist truth teller
the woman who never bites her tongue is coming to kbla talk 1580 and baby the conversations
are about to be unmatched every friday she's going to be lit noon to 2 p.m and back again 4 to 6 p.m
starting friday july 17th only on kbla talk 1580 amanda seals keeping it real keeping it raw and
keeping it rooted politics pop culture black excellence the stuff they don't want us talking
about amanda's talking about all of it you keep interrupting me when i'm talking and you don't
want to hear the point that i'm gonna make the point and yet you want me to respect your point
and that's not how a debate works this is not your average radio show this is a seal's summer
fridays noon to 2 4 to 6 starting friday july 17th only on kbla talk 1580 don't just listen tune in
want to hear the
of
and
the
of